plaingreenloans.com 2019-02-01

# Privacy Policy and Your Personal Information | Plain Green Loans

Plain Green is Providing You the Following Information in a Manner Consistent With Principles Under United States Federal Law.

FACTS| WHAT DOES PLAIN GREEN, LLC DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?  
---|---  
 **Why?** | Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires lenders to tell you how they collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.  
**What?** | The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include: 

  * Social Security number and income
  * Account balances and payment history
  * Credit history and credit scores

**How?** | All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal information; the reasons Plain Green, LLC chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.  
Reasons we can share your personal information| Does Plain Green, LLC share?| Can you limit this sharing?  
---|---|---  
 **For our everyday business purposes -**  
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus | YES | NO  
**For our marketing purposes -**  
to offer our products and services to you | YES | NO  
**For joint marketing** with other financial companies | YES | NO  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -**  
information about your transactions and experiences | YES | NO  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -**  
information about your creditworthiness | YES | NO  
**For our affiliates to market to you** | YES | NO  
**For non-affiliates to market to you** | NO | WE DO NOT SHARE  
**To limit our sharing** | 

  * Call us at: (866) 420-7157; or
  * Contact us via email: [support@plaingreenloans.com](mailto:support@plaingreenloans.com)

**Please note:**

If you are a _new_ customer, we may begin sharing your information as soon as the same day that you apply for a loan. When you are _no longer_ our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice. However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.  
  
---|---  
**Questions?** | 

Call (866) 420-7157 or go to [www.plaingreenloans.com](https://www.plaingreenloans.com/content/).  
  
Who we are  
---  
 **Who is providing this notice?** | 

Plain Green, LLC, a wholly owned limited liability company of the Chippewa Cree Tribe of the Rocky Boy’s Reservation, a federally recognized tribe and its affiliates as listed below.  
  
What We Do  
 **How does Plain Green, LLC protect my personal information?** | To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.   
We also maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards. Only authorized employees have access.  
**How does Plain Green, LLC collect my personal information?** | We collect your personal information, for example, when you 

  * Apply for a loan
  * Give us your income information
  * Provide employment information
  * Provide account information
  * Give us your contact information

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.  
  
**Why can't I limit all sharing?** | Federal law gives you the right to limit only: 

  * Sharing for affiliates everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness
  * affiliates from using your information to market to you
  * Sharing for non-affiliates to market to you

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.  
  
Definitions  
---  
 **Affiliates** | Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial or non-financial companies. Some companies include: 

  * Plain Green, LLC
  * Plain Green SPV, LLC
  * Atoske Loan Services, LLC

**Non-Affiliates** | Financial and non-financial companies not related by common ownership or control. 

  * _Non-affiliates we share with can include companies to market only our products and services to you, to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus._

**Joint Marketing** | 

A formal agreement between companies that together market products or services to you.

  * _Our joint marketing partners may include financial product companies or service companies_

Other Important Information  
---  
  
**"Do not track":** When someone visits the Plain Green website, a cookie is placed on the visitor's computer (if the visitor accepts cookies). The cookie we place on your computer does not contain any of your personally identifiable information. Plain Green advertises its products and services on websites that you may visit, and Plain Green uses service providers to place such advertisements. Those service providers (such as Google, Microsoft or Yahoo) may use cookies placed on your computer to show you advertisements for Plain Green services on other websites. You can opt-out from service providers' and/or marketers' use of cookies in this manner by visiting each service provider's advertising opt-out page or by utilizing "do not track" functionality in your web browser. If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the Plain Green website, you will not be able to subscribe to the service offerings on the Plain Green website.
